{
    "questions":[
        {
            "question": "A site of historic peace negotiations, the presidential retreat Camp David is located in what U.S. state?",
            "option1": "Michigan",
            "option2": "Maryland",
            "option3": "Utah",
            "option4": "New York",
            "ans": "Maryland"
        },
        {
            "question": "A sign with the Spanish word 'salida' on it indicates what?",
            "option1": "Salad",
            "option2": "Entrance",
            "option3": "Steam",
            "option4": "Exit",
            "ans": "Exit"
        },
        {
            "question": "A tea cozy is commonly made out of what material?",
            "option1": "Cardboard",
            "option2": "Paper",
            "option3": "Cloth",
            "option4": "Plastic",
            "ans": "Cloth" 
        },        
        {
            "question": "A traditional food for the Japanese New Year, mochi is a cake primarily made of what ingredient?",
            "option1": "Rice",
            "option2": "Suger",
            "option3": "Flovor",
            "option4": "Glutinous rice",
            "ans": "Rice" 
        },
        {
            "question": "A Web site that no longer exists will often prompt the phrase 'Not Found' and what code number?",
            "option1": "501",
            "option2": "404",
            "option3": "400",
            "option4": "721",
            "ans": "404"  
        },
        {
            "question": "At CS:GO ESL One Cologne 2014 Semi Final, which player successfully defused a bomb while burning in fire?",
            "option1": "olofmeister",
            "option2": "aizy",
            "option3": "JW",
            "option4": "flusha",
            "ans": "olofmeister"  
        },
        {
            "question": "According to official lore, whose birth was greeted by a double rainbow over sacred Mt Paektu?",
            "option1": "Kim Jong-un",
            "option2": "Kim Yo-jong",
            "option3": "Kim Jong-il",
            "option4": "Kim Jong-nam",
            "ans": "Kim Jong-il"  
        },
        {
            "question": "According to the actress, Nichelle Nichols only stayed on what TV series because Martin Luther King, Jr. told her to?",
            "option1": "Star Trek",
            "option2": "The Lieutenant",
            "option3": "Tarzan",
            "option4": "Insight",
            "ans": "Star Trek"  
        },
        {
            "question": "According to U.S. law, what should never be carried flat or horizontally, but always aloft and free?",
            "option1": "U.S. Navy Flag",
            "option2": "U.S. Flag",
            "option3": "U.S. Army Flag",
            "option4": "U.S. Air Force Flag",
            "ans": "U.S. Flag"  
        },
        {
            "question": "Advertised as a 'Decision Engine', Bing is a Web Site most similar in function to which of the following?",
            "option1": "Yahoo",
            "option2": "Yandex",
            "option3": "DuckDuckGo",
            "option4": "Google",
            "ans": "Google"  
        },
        {
            "question": "After Russia, what is the largest country in the world by land area?",
            "option1": "India",
            "option2": "U.S",
            "option3": "Canada",
            "option4": "People's Republic of China",
            "ans": "Canada"  
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the first reusable spacecraft?",
            "option1": "Crew Dragon",
            "option2": "Boeing Starliner",
            "option3": "Starship",
            "option4": "Space Shuttle",
            "ans": "Space Shuttle"  
        },
        {
            "question": "Where does us airways flight 1549 landed?",
            "option1": "Great South Bay",
            "option2": "LaGuardia Airport",
            "option3": "Seattle Tacoma International Airport",
            "option4": "Hudson River",
            "ans": "Hudson River"  
        },
        {
            "question": "An iconic 1964 painting by Rene Magritte depicts a businessman in a bowler hat who face is obscured by a what?",
            "option1": "WaterMelon",
            "option2": "Lemon",
            "option3": "Apple",
            "option4": "Dog",
            "ans": "Apple"  
        },
        {
            "question": "Armbands are popular accessories for which of these tech gadgets?",
            "option1": "iPhone",
            "option2": "iPad",
            "option3": "iPod",
            "option4": "iMac",
            "ans": "iPod"  
        },
        {
            "question": "Which war was called 'The War to End all Wars but It ended nothing' in BattleField 1 campaign mission 'Storm of Steel'?",
            "option1": "World War II",
            "option2": "World War I",
            "option3": "Vietnam War",
            "option4": "Cold War",
            "ans": "World War I"  
        },
        {
            "question": "As its name suggests, Wookieepedia is an online source of information about what sci-fi movie series?",
            "option1": "Star Trek",
            "option2": "Back To Future",
            "option3": "2001 Space Odyssey",
            "option4": "Star Wars",
            "ans": "Star Wars"  
        },
        {
            "question": "Who was the 45th president of the United State?",
            "option1": "Joe Biden",
            "option2": "Rock Johnson",
            "option3": "Donald Trump",
            "option4": "Hillary Clinton",
            "ans": "Donald Trump" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Basra is the chief port of which Persian Gulf country?",
            "option1": "Iran",
            "option2": "Iraq",
            "option3": "Oman",
            "option4": "UAE",
            "ans": "Iraq" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Basic Enlisted Submarine School is a training course offered by which branch of the U.S. military?",
            "option1": "Navy",
            "option2": "Army",
            "option3": "Air Force",
            "option4": "Space Force",
            "ans": "Navy" 
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the place that was used as the name of the R&D project of nuke by the US?",
            "option1": "Los Alamos",
            "option2": "Amber",
            "option3": "Overton",
            "option4": "Manhattan",
            "ans": "Manhattan" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Because it is sold in multiples of 64, computer RAM, or memory, is unavailable in which of these sizes?",
            "option1": "878 MB",
            "option2": "4 GB",
            "option3": "32 GB",
            "option4": "128 GB",
            "ans": "878 MB" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Because the American 'r' sound is rarely pronounced, in what country is Ronald McDonald called 'Donald McDonald'?",
            "option1": "Taiwan",
            "option2": "Thailand",
            "option3": "Japan",
            "option4": "Korea",
            "ans": "Japan" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Best known for their hazelnut-filled Baci chocolates, Perugina is a confectionery based in what country?",
            "option1": "Italy",
            "option2": "France",
            "option3": "United Kingdom",
            "option4": "Germany",
            "ans": "Italy" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Both 'gam' and 'pod' are terms used to describe what group of animals?",
            "option1": "Penguins",
            "option2": "Dolphins",
            "option3": "Whales",
            "option4": "Ants",
            "ans": "Whales" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Carrots are said to be good for the eyes because they enable the body to create what nutrient?",
            "option1": "Calcium",
            "option2": "Lipids",
            "option3": "Vitamin A",
            "option4": "Omega 3",
            "ans": "Vitamin A" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Claiming it is her lucky number, what young singer writes '13' on the back of her hand before shows?",
            "option1": "Noonie Bao",
            "option2": "Rita Ora",
            "option3": "Anne Marie",
            "option4": "Taylor Swift",
            "ans": "Taylor Swift" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Commonly used in Central American cuisine, pernil is meat that comes from what animal?",
            "option1": "Salmon",
            "option2": "Pig",
            "option3": "Goat",
            "option4": "Cow",
            "ans": "Pig" 
        },
        {
            "question": "Deoxiribose, a main component of DNA, is a type of what?",
            "option1": "Oxygen",
            "option2": "Carbon",
            "option3": "Hydrogen",
            "option4": "Sugar",
            "ans": "Sugar" 
        },
        {
            "question": "During World War I, what country introduced a fleet of submarines known as 'U-boats'?",
            "option1": "French",
            "option2": "United States",
            "option3": "Germany",
            "option4": "United Kingdom",
            "ans": "Germany" 
        }
    ], 
    "randomResponse": [
        {
            "1": "It must be A! Gotta be it!"
        },
        {
            "2": "It must be B! Gotta be it!"
        },
        {
            "3": "It must be C! Gotta be it!"
        },
        {
            "4": "It must be D! Gotta be it!"
        },
        {
            "5": "I donno, I guess is A?"
        },
        {
            "6": "I donno, I guess is B?"
        },
        {
            "7": "I donno, I guess is C?"
        },
        {
            "8": "I donno, I guess is D?"
        },
        {
            "9": "It should be A."
        },
        {
            "10": "It should be B."
        },
        {
            "11": "It should be C."
        },
        {
            "12": "It should be D."
        }
    ],
    "beforeRandomResponse": [
        {
            "1": "Hummm..."
        },
        {
            "2": "Errr...."
        },
        {
            "3": "Huh....."
        },
        {
            "4": "Let's see...."
        },
        {
            "5": "Give me a Second...."
        },
        {
            "6": "One moment please...."
        },
        {
            "7": "........."
        },
        {
            "8": "That's tricky, give me a sec..."
        },
        {
            "9": "About that......"
        },
        {
            "10": "Interesting question....."
        }
    ]
}
